totems.co 2015-03-15

# Privacy and Cookie Policy | TOTEMS

We are committed to ensuring the privacy of our users while also making their life online easier by providing a useful and personalised service. This Policy explains how we process data that is sent to us when you use our website. It will be available for you to access through a link in the footer of all of our website pages. If at any point you have questions concerning your personal information or any other aspect of our privacy practices, please get in touch by email at [hello@totems.co](mailto:hello@totems.co "contact totems").

We will refer to any webpage on [http://totems.co](http://totems.co/ "totems") or any of its subdomains as “the Service”. Teleportd Ltd. which builds TOTEMS Analytics will be referred to as “Teleportd”, “we” or “the Company”. “You” means an individual who accesses or uses the Service. The document below which covers matters related to privacy and cookies will be referred to as “the Policy”.

As mentioned in section 8. below, our sites contain links to third party sites (especially in the blog section) which are not subject to this Policy. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any such sites that you may come to visit, if not for the literary thrill then at least for informational purposes.

### Privacy

#### 1\. Information we collect

We collect information when you choose to submit it to us as well as when you use the Service.

In this Policy, “Personal Information” means any information about an identifiable individual, as defined under applicable laws. The Personal Information we collect that you submit using the Service may include:

  * full name
  * company name
  * business type
  * postal address
  * company VAT number
  * email address

or any other specific Personal Information. In some cases, the Personal Information we will ask you to provide will be mandatory to access some parts of the Service. If you do not provide this Personal Information, your access to that particular part of the Service may be limited or disabled.

#### 2\. How we use that Information

We use the information we collect to send you personalised emails as well as to provide you with order and billing information.

#### 3\. Sharing personal information

As mentioned before, we are committed to protecting your personal information. We will never disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your consent except:

_Disclosure for legal reasons_

We reserve the right to communicate your Personal Information to third parties making a request for us to disclose it that is legally compliant, including in the context of investigations of any potential violation, to detect or prevent security breaches, fraud or technical issues,

_Changes in our business_

If the assets that Teleportd Ltd use to operate its business are acquired by a third party, we may transfer personal data we then hold to that party. If Teleportd Ltd buys or sells subsidiaries or business units and if in such transactions Personal Information is one of the transferred assets, this Personal Information would remain subject to the commitments made in this Policy or equivalent.

_Other cases_

We reserve the right to communicate your Personal Information to third parties to protect the rights or property of the Company and its customers, and when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of the Company, its employees and customers or the public.

#### 4\. Children under the age of 13

No part of the Service is designed or intended to attract anyone under 13. We do not seek to collect or maintain information from those under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not provide us any information about yourself, including your name, address, telephone number or email address. If we discover that we have received information about a child under the age of 13 we will immediately and securely delete that information.

#### 5\. Communications

We may occasionally send you communications (by physical mail or email) as a consequence of your use of the Service. You can update the preferences regarding the receipt of such communications in the Account Settings section available in the top right hand side menu of our website.

#### 6\. Access to Personal Information you submit

Personal information collected on the Service may be stored and processed in France, the United Kingdom or any other country in which the company operates, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside your country. As per section 4. of the present Policy, we will not supply your Personal Information to a third party unless explicitly authorised by you to do so. The only circumstances in which we will provide any of your personal data to a third party for non-commercial purposes are those contained in the section 4. of this Policy.

#### 7\. Security of Personal Information

All the information you give to us is stored in France or the UK on secure servers that are protected in secure facilities including firewall protection. We have implemented such technology and security features ourselves or purchased them from specialised third parties, and we maintain strict internal guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your Personal Information from unauthorised access or improper use. Backups are run to prevent loss of information, and we will continue to enhance security as new technology becomes available.

While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Here is where you come in: you can play an important role in keeping your personal information secure by maintaining the confidentiality of your password used on Instagram. We recommend that you change your password from time to time for additional security. Please contact Instagram immediately ([support@instagram.com](mailto:support@instagram.com "support nitrogram")) if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet user or any other breach of security.

As mentioned previously, we have security measures in place to protect our customer database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains each user’s responsibility:

  * to ensure against use by anyone else of the Service through the machine uses while logged on to the Service.
  * to log off or exit from the Service when not using it.
  * to keep his/her password secret.

#### 8\. Third party sites and services

The Service may contain links to third-party websites, products and services, such as social networking sites (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, etc…) and third parties who may offer additional products and services through the Service. Information collected by third parties, is governed by the third parties’ privacy practices.

### Cookies

#### 9\. What cookies are

Cookies are small text files which a website may put on your computer or mobile device when you first visit a site or page. The cookie will help the website, or another website, to identify your device the next time you visit. We use the term “Cookies” in this Policy to refer to all files that collect information in this way. Cookies can for example help us to remember your username and preferences, or analyse how well our website is performing. Certain Cookies contain personal information – for example, if you click to “remember me” when logging in, a Cookie will store the token associated with your Instagram account. Most Cookies won’t collect information that identifies you, and will instead collect more general information such as how you arrive at and use the Service, or your general location.

#### **1** 0\. Cookies on the Service

_Our cookies_

Below are the names and purpose of the cookies we use on the Service:

Name | Purpose  
---|---  
ng-sid | a Cookie to identify you when you visit our Service again and prevent you from needing to authenticate anew with your Instagram credentials  
  
_Third-party cookies_

When you use our Service, you may notice some Cookies that aren’t related to Teleportd Ltd. If you go on to a web page that contains embedded content (for example from Vimeo) you may be sent Cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these Cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their Cookies and how to manage them.

Third Party | Comment  
---|---  
Google | We advertise on third-party websites such as Google. Google uses its own tracking Cookies and the data taken is not confidential or interchangeable.  
Google Analytics  
MixPanel | We use third-party Cookies to better nderstand how our users use the Service. This enables us to improve app experience. Data taken is not confidential or interchangeable.  
Facebook  
Twitter | Sharing content through social networks like Facebook and Twitter can trigger Cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these and we suggest you check the respective websites for more information about them.  
  
#### 11\. Managing Cookies

Most browsers are set-up to accept cookies. You can set your browser to stop cookies being placed on your computer, knowing that this may lead to a sub-optimal experience of our Service. Please refer to your Internet browser for instructions regarding the management of Cookies.

#### 12\. Changes to this Policy

This Policy is effective from January 15 2013. From time to time we may make changes to this privacy policy statement to reflect any changes to our practices in accordance with changes to legislation, best practice or website enhancements.

#### 13\. Getting in touch with us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Policy or about our privacy practices, please get in touch at hello@totems.co.
